Register of the Rodney Kennedy-Minott Papers, 1967-1994
Hoover Institution Archives
- Ambassador to Sweden office file, 1977-1980
  - 1980
    - Memoranda
      - May (Box-folder 20: 5)
      - (handwritten notes and telegram are enclosed), June (Box-folder 20: 6)
      - July (Box-folder 20: 7)
      - August (Box-folder 20: 8)
      - September (Box-folder 20: 9)
    - Schedules
      - January (Box-folder 20: 10)
      - February (Box-folder 20: 11)
      - March (Box-folder 20: 12)
      - April (Box-folder 20: 13)
      - May (Box-folder 20: 14)
      - June (Box-folder 20: 15)
      - July (Box-folder 20: 16)
      - August (Box-folder 20: 17)
      - (includes handwritten notes), September (Box-folder 20: 18)
    - Newsletters
      - February (Box-folder 20: 19)
      - March (Box-folder 20: 20)
      - April (Box-folder 20: 21)
      - May (Box-folder 20: 22)
      - June (Box-folder 20: 23)
      - September (Box-folder 20: 24)
    - Notes (handwritten) (Box-folder 20: 25)
    - Telegrams
      - January (Box-folder 21: 1)
      - February (Box-folder 21: 2)
      - March (Box-folder 21: 3)
      - April (Box-folder 21: 4)
      - May (Box-folder 21: 5)
      - June (Box-folder 21: 6)
      - July (Box-folder 21: 7)
      - August (Box-folder 21: 8)
    - Printed matter (Box-folder 21: 9)
    - Clippings (Box-folder 21: 10)
  - Official travel, 1977-1980
    - 1977 (Box-folder 21: 11)
    - 1978 (Box-folder 21: 12)
    - 1979 (Box-folder 21: 13)
    - 1980 (Box-folder 21: 14)
  - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 21: 15)
  - Social life in Sweden
    - Undated (Box-folder 21: 16)
    - 1977
      - September (Box-folder 21: 17)
      - October (Box-folder 21: 18)
      - November (Box-folder 21: 19)
      - December (Box-folder 21: 20)
    - 1978
      - General (Box-folder 21: 21)
      - January (Box-folder 21: 22)
      - February (Box-folder 21: 23)
      - March (Box-folder 21: 24)
      - April (Box-folder 21: 25)
      - May (Box-folder 21: 26)
      - June (Box-folder 21: 27)
      - July (Box-folder 21: 28)
      - August (Box-folder 21: 29)
      - September (Box-folder 21: 30)
      - October (Box-folder 22: 1)
      - November (Box-folder 22: 2)
      - December (Box-folder 22: 3)
    - 1979
      - January (Box-folder 22: 4)
      - February (Box-folder 22: 5)
      - March (Box-folder 22: 6)
      - April (Box-folder 22: 7)
      - May (Box-folder 22: 8)
      - June (Box-folder 22: 9)
      - July (Box-folder 22: 10)
      - August (Box-folder 22: 11)
      - September (Box-folder 22: 12)
      - October (Box-folder 22: 13)
      - November (Box-folder 22: 14)
      - December (Box-folder 22: 15)
    - 1980
      - January (Box-folder 22: 16)
      - February (Box-folder 22: 17)
      - March (Box-folder 22: 18)
      - April (Box-folder 22: 19)
      - May (Box-folder 22: 20)
      - June (Box-folder 23: 1)
      - July (Box-folder 23: 2)
      - August (Box-folder 23: 3)
      - September (Box-folder 23: 4)
  - Nobel Prize Ceremonies, 1977-1979
    - General (postcard and brochures are enclosed) (Box-folder 23: 5)
      - 1977
        - Schedule (Box-folder 23: 6)
        - Nobel Prize recipients - biographical sketches and clippings (Box-folder 23: 7)
        - Translation of the speeches (Box-folder 23: 8)
        - Press release and printed matter (Box-folder 23: 9)
        - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 23: 10)
      - 1978
        - Schedule (Box-folder 23: 11)
        - Nobel Prize recipients (Box-folder 23: 12)
        - Translation of the speeches (Box-folder 23: 13)
        - Memorandum on procedure and presentation ceremony (Box-folder 23: 14)
        - Miscellaneous
          - Lunch & dinner schedule (Box-folder 23: 15)
          - Telegram (Box-folder 23: 16)
          - General Motors Foundation visit - printed matter (Box-folder 23: 17)
          - Newsletter & brochure (Box-folder 23: 18)
      - 1979
        - Schedule (Box-folder 23: 19)
        - Nobel Prize recipients (Box-folder 23: 20)
        - Translation of the speeches (Box-folder 23: 21)
        - Banquets and receptions (Box-folder 23: 22)
      - Correspondence
        - Chapman, Albert S. (Box-folder 24: 1)
        - Ramel, Stig (Box-folder 24: 2)
        - Schriver, Dorothy (Box-folder 24: 3)
      - Telegrams (Box-folder 24: 4)
  - State Department Communications, 1975-1980
    - 1975
      - Sweden: The Pragmatic Neutral, a paper written by Major John L. Golden (typescript) (Box-folder 24: 5)
    - 1976
      - Report on Scandinavia - includes a memo dated, 1977 (Box-folder 24: 6)
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 24: 7)
    - 1978
      - Report - Relates to the implementation of U.S. policy in Sweden (Box-folder 24: 8)
      - Bureau of European Affairs - List of Offices (Box-folder 24: 9)
      - Extradition Certificate (Box-folder 24: 10)
    - 1979
      - Proposed Foreign Service Act - printed copy (Box-folder 24: 11)
      - American Foreign Service Association - Statement and Guidelines (Box-folder 24: 12)
      - Correspondence relating to Evaluation Report of a staff member of American Embassy in Sweden (Box-folder 24: 13)
      - List of Members of the U.S. Senate (Box-folder 24: 14)
    - 1980
      - Report on the general strike in Sweden, May 1980 (Box-folder 24: 15)
      - Telegrams (includes a printed copy of a telegram relating to the travel restrictions in Sweden) (Box-folder 24: 16)
  - American Foreign Policy Subject File, 1977-1980
    - General
      - Notes (handwritten) (Box-folder 24: 17)
      - Printed matter (Box-folder 24: 18)
      - Wireless files (Box-folder 24: 19)
      - Press release (Box-folder 24: 20)
      - Telegrams (Box-folder 24: 21)
    - Afghanistan (printed matter only) (Box-folder 24: 22)
    - Africa (note and printed matter) (Box-folder 24: 23)
    - Australia (memorandum and correspondence) (Box-folder 24: 24)
    - China (printed matter and card) (Box-folder 24: 25)
    - Iran
      - Press release (Box-folder 24: 26)
      - News summary (Box-folder 24: 27)
      - Printed matter (Box-folder 24: 28)
      - Telegram (Box-folder 24: 29)
      - Wireless File (Box-folder 24: 30)
      - Clipping and brochure (Box-folder 24: 31)
    - Middle East (printed matter only) (Box-folder 24: 32)
    - Panama (typescript article along with a memorandum and a letter) (Box-folder 24: 33)
    - Soviet Union
      - Report (Box-folder 24: 34)
      - Communique (Box-folder 24: 35)
      - Wireless File (Box-folder 24: 36)
      - Printed matter (Box-folder 24: 37)
    - Sweden
      - General
        - "The Ambassador in Sweden," A Media Overview (Box-folder 24: 38)
        - "Comparative Study of the U.S. and Sweden: Energy and the Quality of Life, " - a study (Box-folder 24: 39)
      - Swedish Energy Policy (handwritten notes enclosed) (Box-folder 24: 40)
      - Swedish Foreign Policy
        - Article in Swedish (Box-folder 24: 41)
        - "Relief Instead of Development Aid," Translation of article by Gunnar Myrdal in Ekonomisk Debatt, 1980 (Box-folder 24: 42)
        - Speech, given by Deputy Director General Folke Gors at the inauguration ceremony at Goteborg - Landvetter Airport, October 1, 1977 (Box-folder 24: 43)
      - Shipping Policy - Memorandum (Box-folder 24: 44)
      - Carter Administration
        - Printed Matter (Box-folder 24: 45)
        - Draft of a letter to President Jimmy Carter written by Jack Perry (Box-folder 24: 46)
        - "Farewell to Sweden," an article (Box-folder 24: 47)
        - Newsletter (Box-folder 24: 48)
        - Ambassador's Comments about Carter (Box-folder 24: 49)
        - Clippings (Ambassador's handwritten notes and a typed note are enclosed), 1990 (Box-folder 24: 50)
      - Miscellaneous
        - "Cogeneration in Western Europe and its Application in California " - a study by the California Foundation on the Environment and the Economy, Aug. 1980 (Box-folder 24: 51)
        - Editorial - Aftonbladet, 1975 September 22 (Box-folder 24: 52)
        - Correspondence (includes some in Swedish) (Box-folder 24: 53)
        - "Secret Trans-World Organization for Punishment" (printed copy) (Box-folder 24: 54)
        - Memorandum on Ambassadorial Speeches, Sept. 8, 1977 (Box-folder 24: 55)
  - Ambassador's Efficiency Report and Resignation, 1980 (Box-folder 24: 56)
- Post ambassador years, 1980-1982
  Correspondence, reports and social invitations received by Rodney Kennedy-Minott in the years following his resignation as Ambassador to Sweden
  - Correspondence
    - Carter, Jimmy, 1981 (Box-folder 25: 1)
    - Christopher, Warren, 1981 (Box-folder 25: 2)
    - Hinkley, Gerald M., 1981 (Box-folder 25: 3)
    - Methven, Bruce E., 1981 (Box-folder 25: 4)
    - Mondale, Walter F., 1981-1985 (Box-folder 25: 5)
    - Strauss, Harlan J., 1981 (Box-folder 25: 6)
    - Vest, George S., 1981 (Box-folder 25: 7)
  - Impressions of Rodney Kennedy-Minott from his trip to Sweden in, October, 1982 (Box-folder 25: 8)
  - Social Invitations, (Ambassador's typed notes are enclosed), 1980-1981 (Box-folder 25: 9)
  - Schedules, 1982 (Box-folder 25: 10)
  - Typescript copies of articles translated from Svensha Dogblodet, April 5 and April 9, 1981 (Box-folder 25: 11)
- Miscellaneous file, 1976-1980
  Includes brochures, program, correspondence, printed matter, newsletter, resumes and letters of recommendation, copies of songs, recipe, menu, map, parking permit, calling cards and postcards
  - Ambassador's remarks about Carter Campaign of 1976, his observations regarding one of his staff members (a cassette tape, typed and printed copies) (Box-folder 25: 12)
  - Brochures (Box-folder 25: 13)
  - Leaflets (Box-folder 25: 14)
  - Conference program (Box-folder 25: 15)
  - Correspondence (Box-folder 25: 16)
  - Printed matter (Box-folder 25: 17)
  - Newsletter (Box-folder 25: 18)
  - Resume and recommendation letters (Box-folder 25: 19)
  - Music (Box-folder 25: 20)
  - Maps and parking permit (Box-folder 25: 21)
  - Greetings cards (Box-folder 25: 22)
  - Calling cards (Box-folder 25: 23)
  - General
    - Telephone messages (Box-folder 25: 24)
    - Names and addresses (Box-folder 25: 25)
    - Notes (some handwritten) (Box-folder 25: 26)
    - Stickers (Box-folder 25: 27)
    - Recipe and menus (Box-folder 25: 28)
- Incremental materials (Box 26-29)
  Not described
- Declassified U.S. Government records, 1978
  Formerly security-classified records of the U.S. government. Includes some government records determined by the government to be unclassified. Arranged chronologically by date of release by Hoover
  - 2011 September release of records, 1978 (Box 29)
    Unclassified records, chiefly photocopies of cables from the American embassy, Stockholm
  - 2017 release of records, 1977-1980
- Phonotapes, 1976
  Interview of President Jimmy Carter by Bill Moyers
- Photographs, 1967-1980
  See Photocard catalog